Fifteen passengers were burned alive when a passenger bus was set on fire by an
unknown min in Pakistan's southwestern Balchistan province, an official said.
Naseer Ahmed Naseer, deputy commissioner in the city of said four men on motorcycles
initially opened fire on a parked passenger bus at a hotel.
Naseer Ahmed Naseer,
Naseer Ahmed Naseer, deputy commissioner in the city of said four men on motorcycles
initially opened fire on a parked passenger bus at a hotel.
The armed men then came close to the bus and splashed petrol, setting it on fire, he
He said most of the dead were either children or women.
said. He said most of the dead were either children or women.
The armed men then came close to the bus and splashed petrol, setting it on fire, he
Balochistan, near the Afghan border, is rich in natural resources, but it is also in
under a riot.
under a Balochistan, near the Afghan border, is rich in natural resources, but it is
also in under a riot.
Militants there have for years complained that the central government has paid
little attention to them and their economic needs.
They have been fighting Pakistani military forces for self -rule.